aypearl.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy policy - Wholesale Jewelry center in China at AYpearl.com

### Privacy Policy 

At [AYPearl.com](http://www.aypearl.com/), we respect and protect our customers' privacy when we devote ourselves to providing excellent services and jewelry with good quality. Your personal information collected to offer better service for you is handled safely and responsibly. We have instituted politics intended to ensure that they are not sold or rented to other companies. The following are details of our privacy policy. 

#### Quality , Selection and Value 

As the leading jewelry manufacturer in China, we offer our customers outstanding service by offering you the widest selection of fine jewelry directly from our network with no limits of sum and quantity. Unlike most of the online jewelers, we bypass the middlemen in the traditional distribution channels and save 75% for our customers. On our website, customers will get the widest selection of the highest quality, finest jewelry at low prices. We can deliver our products efficiently to more than 220 countries and areas.

#### Cookies

To avoid the loss of information due to computer virus and spy software, we use cookie to record all information in customers' computers. There is no need for customers to worry that they can not order goods normally when cookie is restricted.

#### Session

Session is used to identify customers and record the information of customer's shopping cart. Therefore, others can not get the customers' information. Furthermore, session clears them automatically when customers log out. 

#### How Is The Information Used?

We may use your information in a number of ways, including the following: to institute sale and promotion plans:to send our emails or catalogs to our customers about products..

#### Is The Information Shared?

The information gathered is used only inside our company. We provide more services for our customers with their information and strictly control our internal staff’s visits to customer’s information to avoid loss of the info.

#### Will the AYPearl.com privacy policy change?

We may change or enhance our policy to improve our service. If we do change our policy, we will note all changes on our web site. A message will be displayed on our home page for a period of time showing that changes have been made. We also may send an e-mail describing the changes. You are welcome to refer to this policy every time you are considering making a purchase.
